thecoolhunter.co.uk 2008-10-06

# thecoolhunter - Privacy Statement

**What personal information is collected?**  
When you subscribe to the Cool Hunter mailing list you enter your name and email address.

**Will personal information be given to anyone else?**  
The Cool Hunter respects your privacy and will never give out or sell your details to anyone else.

**Security of personal information**  
The Cool Hunter stores all personal information in a secure database that is encrypted.

**Can I opt out?**  
If you decide that you no longer wish to receive our emails, you can unsubscribe by sending us a reply email or by using the contact page. You will be removed from the list as soon as possible.

**Access and correction**  
Under the Privacy Act, you have a right to seek access to information that Cool Hunter holds about you. You also have the right to ask us to correct information about you that is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date. If you wish to access the personal information that we hold about you, just send us an email via the contact page.

**Links to other websites**  
The Cool Hunter website often contains links to third party websites. We cannot be held responsible for the content or privacy policies of third party websites and suggest you read the privacy policy of each site you visit.  
**  
Additional privacy information and how to contact The Cool Hunter**  
If you feel that The Cool Hunter is not complying with this Privacy Policy, or if you have other privacy concerns, please email using the contact page.
